Mobile: +91 8296169647 | E-mail:keerti.shetty11@gmail.com | Location :Bangalore

Career Objective:

Strongly dedicated and resourceful -Talent Acquisition Executive at Morgan Stanley by AMS with 4 years of experience. Currently working as a sourcer and candidate coordinator helping organization to build their business by recruiting strong and skilled resources.

Employment Details:

1. Executive - Talent Acquisition

Morgan Stanley through AMS, Bengaluru, Karnataka (From Feb 2022-Present)

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Sourcing for the multiple requirements using different platforms/social media.
- Holds hands on experience on sourcing from different portals(X-ray searches, references etc).
- ➤ Candidate Management activities complete focus into scheduling and coordination.
- > Scheduling discussions for candidates from technical till HR with panels from particular business units including global panels.
- Strong proficiency with Taleo, Eight Fold, and Microsoft Office applications.
- Primary Point of Contact between business unit, Agencies, vendors & candidates.
- Organizing super days and hiring drives.
- Extensive recruiting and applicant tracking system experience.
- Scheduling bi-weekly catch up calls between candidates and hiring managers till the Date Of Joining.
- Outstanding multitasking abilities.
- Experience in working for both Technology and Non Tech Recruitment.
- 2. Marketing and Operation coordinator

First International Specialized Vehicles, UAE

(From Jul 2017- Dec 2018)

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Responsible for spare parts sales and Annual Maintenance Contract (AMC) of eclectic vehicles right from receiving the inquiry till the payment recovery of the same.
- Responsible for coordination of all after sale services of electric vehicles between the client and the operation department.
- > Strong customer delivery experience, managing and handling deals using Focus-ERP software.

Reerti Shetty

Mobile: +91 8296169647 | E-mail:keerti.shetty11@gmail.com | Location :Bangalore

- Responsible to schedule for the AMC visit and preparing maintenance reports.
- Conducting Team Building Activities and Monthly Presentations.
- Maintaining Reports-Daily, Weekly and Monthly basis.
- Working on Mails, Part of client calls, meetings and also managed people in the absence of Team Lead.
- 3. Marketing Coordinator

Standex FZE, UAE

(From October 2016- May 2017)

Duties and Responsibilities:

- > Lead generation, taking appointments, setting up meetings doing required follow-ups with clients.
- > Coordinating with installation team and handling the projects from beginning till the handover and recovery of the payments.
- Organizing and coordinating exhibitions includes events such as Big 5, Intersec, Gulf food, light Middle East, Indian Property Show etc.

Education

- MBA 72.85% (Marketing and Finance) from Rani Channamma University, Belagavi
- ➤ BCA 78% from Karnataka University Dharwad.

Major Achievements

- Got Star performer award within six months of joining.
- Appreciation from the clients and management for good work.
- Dedicated and Efficient employee.
- Training completed: Communicative skills for consultants, MBA in a Day.

Skills

- Applicant Tracking Systems ,Full-life Cycle Recruiting , Sourcing, Diversity hiring ,Technical Recruiting , IT and Non IT Recruitment, Candidate Experience.
- Programming Languages: C, C++, HTML, Python, R(Basic), MS (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)

Declaration

I do hereby declare that the information furnished above is correct to the best of my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the particulars.

Signature

Place: